Register of the Congo (Democratic Republic) subject collection, 1960-2001
Hoover Institution Archives
Congo (Democratic Republic) Subject Collection,
1960-2001
XX837
18 manuscript boxes (7.5 linear feet)
Hoover Institution Archives Stanford, California 94305-6010
Electronic bulletins, pamphlets, bulletins, serial issues, speeches, leaflets, reports, and other printed matter, relating to political, social and economic conditions in the Democratic Republic of the Congo.
Administrative Information
Access
Collection open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Access Points
Congo (Democratic Republic); Africa
Series Description
- SUBJECT FILE, 1960-1995. (Box 1)
  Bulletins, leaflets, newsletter, pamphlets, reports, serial issues and speeches relating to economic, political and social conditions in Zaire
- INTERNATIONAL SUPPORT GROUPS, 1990. (Box 1)
  Leaflet, newsletter and printed matter relating to political conditions in Zaire and its relationship with the United States
- REVOLUTIONARY MOVEMENTS, 1984-1995. (Box 1)
  Brochures, printed matter and printed copy of an interview relating to the revolutionary movements in Zaire
Container List
See card catalog for increments that may have been received after February 1995
- SUBJECT FILE, 1960-1995
  - General (Box 1.)
  - Economy
  - Education
  - Health - Acquired Immune Deficiency System (AIDS)
  - Human rights
  - Politics and government
  - Religion
  - Women
- INTERNATIONAL SUPPORT GROUPS, 1990.
  - U.S. Congo Friendship Committee (Box 1.)
- REVOLUTIONARY MOVEMENTS, 1984-1995
  - General (Box 1.)
  - Printed copy. Interview with M. Felix Mukulubundu
- Incremental materials (Box 2-18)
  This addition to the collection has not yet been described. Please let the Hoover Institution Archives know if you would like to see this material described.